Guide to the Emilie F. Miller papers, 1987-1991
George Mason University Libraries
- Emilie F.Miller Collection
  - Mrs Carey [ Widening Lee Highway] (Folder 8, Box 14)
  - Christopfferson, Scott A. [Recommendation] (Folder 9, Box 14)
  - Clean Indoor Act (Folder 10, Box 14)
  - Columbia Pines Citizens Association Road Maintenance (Folder 11, Box 14)
  - Constituent Call Forms (Folder 12, Box 14)
  - Cornelius A. Dolby - Move of Virginia Employment Commission (Folder 13, Box 14)
  - Traffic Parking Zonning Violation [Dale Starns, Egon Wick, Culmore, Woodrow Wilson Action] (Folder 14, Box 14)
  - Dental Hygienists Letters [H.Bill 1117] 1990 (Folder 15, Box 14)
  - David Francis Giarrusso - Hate Note to Senator Miller February 20,1989 (Folder 16, Box 14)
  - Downzoning Letters [1 of 4] 1990 (Folder 17, Box 14)
  - Downzoning Letters [2 of 4] 1990 (Folder 18, Box 14)
  - Down zoning Letters [3 of 4] 1990 (Folder 19, Box 14)
  - Down zoning Letters [4 of 4] 1990 (Folder 20, Box 14)
  - Drug and Alcohol 1990 (Folder 21, Box 14)
  - Roads - Repair of Patches (Folder 22, Box 14)
  - Emil Franks Clozaril Coverage by Medicaid (Folder 23, Box 14)
  - Fairfax Villa - Street Repair (Folder 24, Box 14)
  - Forest ,John Paul II [Correspondence] (Folder 25, Box 14)
  - General Correspondence [January 31,1990] January 31,1990 (Folder 26, Box 14)
  - General Correspondence [February 1990] February, 1990 (Folder 27, Box 14)
  - General Correspondence [March, 1990] March, 1990 (Folder 28, Box 14)
  - General Correspondence [April, 1990] April, 1990 (Folder 29, Box 14)
  - General Correspondence [May, 1990] May, 1990 (Folder 30, Box 14)
  - General Correspondence [June ,1990] June, 1990 (Folder 31, Box 14)
  - General Correspondence [July, 1990] July, 1990 (Folder 32, Box 14)
  - General Correspondence [August, 1990] August, 1990 (Folder 33, Box 14)
  - General Correspondence [September, 1990] September, 1990 (Folder 34, Box 14)
  - General Correspondence [October, 1990] October, 1990 (Folder 35, Box 14)
  - General Correspondence [November 1990] November, 1990 (Folder 36, Box 14)
  - General Correspondence [December ,1990] December, 1990 (Folder 37, Box 14)
  - General Correspondence [March, 1991] March, 1991 (Folder 38, Box 14)
  - General Correspondence [April, 1991] April, 1991 (Folder 39, Box 14)
  - General Correspondence [May, 1991] May, 1991 (Folder 40, Box 14)
  - General Correspondence [June, 1991] June, 1991 (Folder 41, Box 14)
  - General Correspondence [July, 1991] July, 1991 (Folder 42, Box 14)
  - General Correspondence [August ,1991] August, 1991 (Folder 43, Box 14)
  - General Correspondence [September, 1991] September, 1991 (Folder 44, Box 14)
  - General Correspondence [October, 1991] October, 1991 (Folder 45, Box 14)
  - General Correspondence [November ,1991] November, 1991 (Folder 46, Box 14)
  - Goodwin House [Alternative Budget Plan - VHCA and State] 1991 (Folder 47, Box 14)
  - Greenway Downs Subdivision VDOT Problem (Folder 48, Box 14)
  - House Bill - 721 [Land use Legislation] (Folder 49, Box 14)
  - Holmes Run Village (Folder 50, Box 14)
  - Jane Woods, [Delegate News Clip] 1990 (Folder 51, Box 14)
  - Lakeside Plaza Condominium (Folder 52, Box 14)
  - Congratulations letters (Folder 53, Box 14)
  - Mantua Elementary School [Richmond Visit] 1991 (Folder 54, Box 14)
  - Maynard Hamilton - WWII 50th Anniversary (Folder 55, Box 14)
  - Miriam Wimberly - Blue Cross and Blue Shield [Transfer Policies] (Folder 56, Box 14)
  - Montessori Schools and House Bill - 1035 (Folder 57, Box 14)
  - Skyline Plaza Condominium (Folder 58, Box 14)
  - State Corporation Commission and Virginia Power - Energy Efficiency Concerns 1991 (Folder 59, Box 14)
  - Uniform Certification of Engineers - Letters 1991 (Folder 60, Box 14)
  - Walnut Hills - Sidewalks (Folder 61, Box 14)
  - Willow Spring Civic Association 1989 (Folder 62, Box 14)
  - Yorktown Square Condominiums [ 1 of 2] (Folder 63, Box 14)
  - Yorktown Square Condominiums [2 of 2] (Folder 64, Box 14)
  - State Bill - 821, Admission of Qualified Students 1991 (Folder 1, Box 15)
  - State Bill - 477,Admission of Qualified Students to Public Institution of Higher Education 1990 (Folder 2, Box 15)
  - Alumni Letter- Virginia Military Institute 1991 (Folder 3, Box 15)
  - VMI - Alumni Suit 1990 - 1991 (Folder 4, Box 15)
  - VMI Article [Lex Claudia] December 5,1990 (Folder 5, Box 15)
  - VMI - Bill Budget Amendment 1990 (Folder 6, Box 15)
  - Resolution on VMI (Folder 7, Box 15)
  - VMI Correspondence [1 of 4] 1990 - 1991 (Folder 8, Box 15)
  - VMI Correspondence [2 of 4] 1990 - 1991 (Folder 9, Box 15)
  - VMI Correspondence [3 of 4] 1990 - 1991 (Folder 10, Box 15)
  - VMI Correspondence [4 of 4] 1990 - 1991 (Folder 11, Box 15)
  - VMI Correspondence June, 1991 (Folder 12, Box 15)
  - VMI Correspondence [1 of 2] (Folder 13, Box 15)
  - VMI Correspondence [2 of 2] (Folder 14, Box 15)
  - VMI Crossfire (Folder 15, Box 15)
  - Dick's Response to VMI People 1991 (Folder 16, Box 15)
  - VMI - Gov Wilder Press Release 1990 (Folder 17, Box 15)
  - VMI Information (Folder 18, Box 15)
  - VMI Information Campaign 1991 (Folder 19, Box 15)
  - Legal Defense Funds for VMI 1991 (Folder 20, Box 15)
  - VMI Legal References [1 of 2] (Folder 21, Box 15)
  - VMI Legal References [2 of 2] (Folder 22, Box 15)
  - VMI - Letters to AG, Gov, Justice 1990 (Folder 23, Box 15)
  - Letter to Gov Baliles, VMI 1991 (Folder 24, Box 15)
  - Lex Claudia 1991 (Folder 25, Box 15)
  - VMI, Lex Claudia 1992 (Folder 26, Box 15)
  - VMI, Lex Claudia Article 1992 (Folder 27, Box 15)
  - Lex Claudia Edited VMI article [1 of 2] (Folder 28, Box 15)
  - Lex Claudia Edited VMI article [2 of 2] (Folder 29, Box 15)
  - VMI Opinion on 06/17/91, USA Vs Commonwealth of Virginia [1 of 2] June 17,1991 (Folder 30, Box 15)
  - VMI Opinion on 06/17/91, USA Vs Commonwealth of Virginia [2 of 2] June 17,1991 (Folder 31, Box 15)
  - VMI Poll Data 1991 (Folder 32, Box 15)
  - VMI [Anonymous Letters] (Folder 33, Box 15)
  - VMI - Press Articles (Folder 34, Box 15)
  - VMI - Press Articles 1989 (Folder 35, Box 15)
  - VMI - Press Articles [1 of 3] 1990 (Folder 36, Box 15)
  - VMI - Press Articles [2 of 3] 1990 (Folder 37, Box 15)
  - VMI - Press Articles [3 of 3] 1990 (Folder 38, Box 15)
  - Magazine Article on Virginia Military Institute (Folder 39, Box 15)
  - VMI Letters (Folder 40, Box 15)
  - VMI - Press Atlanta Constitution Article (Folder 1, Box 16)
  - VMI Press Clippings 1991 (Folder 2, Box 16)
  - VMI Press - Emilie F. Miller Cited or Quoted [1 of 3] 1990 (Folder 3, Box 16)
  - VMI Press - Emilie F. Miller Cited or Quoted [2 of 3] 1990 (Folder 4, Box 16)
  - VMI Press - Emilie F. Miller Cited or Quoted [3 of 3] 1990 (Folder 5, Box 16)
  - VMI Press 1992 (Folder 6, Box 16)
  - VMI Press Information (Folder 7, Box 16)
  - VMI - Press Release 1990 (Folder 8, Box 16)
  - VMI Speech April, 1989 (Folder 9, Box 16)
  - VMI - Tag,Lottery (Folder 10, Box 16)
  - VMI - Trial Press [1 of 3] (Folder 11, Box 16)
  - VMI - Trial Press [2 of 3] (Folder 12, Box 16)
  - VMI - Trial Press [3 of 3] (Folder 13, Box 16)
  - USA Vs Virginia State and VMI CounterClaim, VMI Alumni (Folder 14, Box 16)
  - VMI Vs USA, Thornburgh (Folder 15, Box 16)
  - Virginia Women Attorney Association on VMI Issue (Folder 16, Box 16)
  - Working for Sex Equity in Insurance Information and Strategic Packet [1 of 4] (Folder 17, Box 16)
  - Working for Sex Equity in Insurance Information and Strategic Packet [2 of 4] (Folder 18, Box 16)
  - Working for Sex Equity in Insurance Information and Strategic Packet [3 of 4] (Folder 19, Box 16)
  - Working for Sex Equity in Insurance Information and Strategic Packet [4 of 4] (Folder 20, Box 16)
  - American Association on Mental Retardation [AAMR] (Folder 1, Box 17)
  - Fairfax County Council of Arts Calendar January, 1991 (Folder 2, Box 17)
  - VHSL Calendar for 1990- 1991 School Year 1990 - 1991 (Folder 3, Box 17)
  - Cardiac Arrest Event, American Heart Association April 25, 1991 (Folder 4, Box 17)
  - Center for Policy Alternatives, Washington D.C. December 16, 1990 (Folder 5, Box 17)
  - Center for Policy Alternatives - Fund Raising Dinner December 11, 1991 (Folder 6, Box 17)
  - National Order of Women Legislators Conference at Mackinac Island,MI August 23- 27,1991 (Folder 7, Box 17)
  - State Legislative Leaders Foundation Conference - Renee Ross,FL March 7 - 9,1991 (Folder 8, Box 17)
  - VACSB- Conference Richmond,VA January 24, 1991 (Folder 9, Box 17)
  - National Women Political Caucus Convention July 12, 1991 (Folder 10, Box 17)
  - Commission on Population Growth and Development, Wintergreen, VA November 21- 22, 1991 (Folder 11, Box 17)
  - Correspondence [1 of 2] April, 1990 (Folder 12, Box 17)
  - Correspondence [2 of 2] April, 1990 (Folder 13, Box 17)
  - Democratic Leadership Council - National Convention in Cleveland May 7, 1991 (Folder 14, Box 17)
  - Department of Health,Human Services Workshops July 26, 1991 (Folder 15, Box 17)
  - Fairfax City Community Calendar 1991 (Folder 16, Box 17)
  - Global Leaders of the South Leadership Forum May 24, 1991 (Folder 17, Box 17)
  - Hawaii's Healthy Start, Honolulu,Hawaii February -7, 1992 (Folder 18, Box 17)
  - Labor Issues - Rebuilding America, San Diego,CA 1991 (Folder 19, Box 17)
  - SBA Legislative Conference- Kansas City November 20, 1991 (Folder 20, Box 17)
  - Letters (Folder 21, Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous Fall Dates 1991 (Folder 22, Box 17)
  - National Conference of State Legislators April 13, 1991 (Folder 23, Box 17)
  - National Conference of State Legislators, State-Federal Meeting May 3, 1991 (Folder 24, Box 17)
  - Photocopies of Blank Senate Schedules (Folder 25, Box 17)
  - Congratulation Letters and Russell for State Senate Letters (Folder 26, Box 17)
  - Schedule Book - January January, 1991 (Folder 27, Box 17)
  - Schedule Book - February February, 1991 (Folder 28, Box 17)
  - Schedule Book - March March, 1991 (Folder 29, Box 17)
  - Schedule Book -September September, 1991 (Folder 30, Box 17)
  - Schedule Book - October October, 1991 (Folder 31, Box 17)
  - Schedule Book -November November, 1991 (Folder 32, Box 17)
  - Schedule Book - 1992 1992 (Folder 33, Box 17)
  - Schedule Information December, 1990 (Folder 34, Box 17)
  - Schedule Information - December to January January 5,1991 (Folder 35, Box 17)
  - Schedule Information [January 6 - 12, 1991] 1991 (Folder 36, Box 17)
  - Schedule Information [January 13-19, 1991] 1991 (Folder 37, Box 17)
  - Schedule Events [January 20-26,1991] 1991 (Folder 38, Box 17)
  - Schedule Events [January 27-February 2,1991] 1991 (Folder 39, Box 17)
  - Schedule Events [February 4-10,1991] 1991 (Folder 40, Box 17)
  - Schedule Events [February 11-17,1991] 1991 (Folder 41, Box 17)
  - Schedule Events [February 18-24,1991] 1991 (Folder 42, Box 17)
  - Schedule Events [February 25-March 3,1991] 1991 (Folder 43, Box 17)
  - Schedule Events [March 4-10,1991] 1991 (Folder 44, Box 17)
  - Schedule Events [March 11-17,1991] 1991 (Folder 45, Box 17)
  - Schedule Events [March 18-24,1991] 1991 (Folder 46, Box 17)
  - Schedule Events [March 25-31,1991] 1991 (Folder 47, Box 17)
  - Schedule Events [April 1-8,1991] 1991 (Folder 48, Box 17)
  - Schedule Events [April 9-15,1991] 1991 (Folder 49, Box 17)
  - Schedule Events [April 16-22,1991] 1991 (Folder 50, Box 17)
  - Schedule Events [April 23-28,1991] 1991 (Folder 51, Box 17)
  - Schedule Events [April 29-May 5,1991] 1991 (Folder 52, Box 17)
  - Schedule Events [May 6-12,1991] 1991 (Folder 53, Box 17)
  - Schedule Events [May 13-20,1991] 1991 (Folder 54, Box 17)
  - Schedule Events [May 21-28,1991] 1991 (Folder 55, Box 17)
  - Schedule Events [May 28-June 2,1991] 1991 (Folder 1, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [June 3-9,1991] 1991 (Folder 2, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [June 10-16,1991] 1991 (Folder 3, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [June 17-23,1991] 1991 (Folder 4, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [June 24-30,1991] 1991 (Folder 5, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [July 4,1991] 1991 (Folder 6, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [July 1-7,1991] 1991 (Folder 7, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [July 8-14,1991] 1991 (Folder 8, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [July 15-21,1991] 1991 (Folder 9, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [July 22-28,1991] 1991 (Folder 10a, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [July 29-August 4,1991] 1991 (Folder 10b, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [August 5-11,1991] 1991 (Folder 11, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [August 12-18,1991] 1991 (Folder 12, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [August 19-25,1991] 1991 (Folder 13, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [August 26-September 1,1991] 1991 (Folder 14, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [September 2-8,1991] 1991 (Folder 15, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [September 9-15,1991] 1991 (Folder 16, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [September 16-22,1991] 1991 (Folder 17, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [September 23-29,1991][1 of 2] 1991 (Folder 18, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [September 23-29,1991][2 of 2] 1991 (Folder 19, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [September 30-October 6,1991] 1991 (Folder 20, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [October 7-10,1991] 1991 (Folder 21, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [October 11-13,1991] 1991 (Folder 22, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [October 14-20,1991] 1991 (Folder 23, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [October 21-27,1991] 1991 (Folder 24, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [October 28-November 3,1991] 1991 (Folder 25, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [November 4-10,1991] 1991 (Folder 26, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [November 11-17,1991] 1991 (Folder 27, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [November 18-19,1991] 1991 (Folder 28, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [November 17-24,1991] 1991 (Folder 29, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [November 25-December 1,1991] 1991 (Folder 30, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [December 2-8,1991] 1991 (Folder 31, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events [December 9-31,1991] 1991 (Folder 32, Box 18)
  - Schedule Events of Woman's National Democratic Club [WNDC] 1991 (Folder 33, Box 18)
  - Schedule - Pending 1991 (Folder 34, Box 18)
  - Southern Legislative Conference [July 20-24] 1991 (Folder 35, Box 18)
  - Southern Legislative Conference ,Pinehurst,NC November 13,1991 (Folder 36, Box 18)
  - NCSL State -Federal Assembly ,Orlando,Florida August 15,1991 (Folder 37, Box 18)
  - NCSL State -Federal Assembly ,Washington D.C. December 11-13,1991 (Folder 38, Box 18)
  - S.E. US and Korea Economic Council ,Charleston,SC November 18-20,1990 (Folder 39, Box 18)
  - Women in Government,Scottsdale,AZ January 2-5,1992 (Folder 40, Box 18)
  - 1991 Congressional Redistricting [1 of 2] 1991 (Folder 1, Box 19)
  - 1991 Congressional Redistricting [2 of 2] 1991 (Folder 2, Box 19)
  - Crack Babies: Maternal and prenatal Drug Exposure and Abuse [SJR11/HJR14] [1 of 12] (Folder 3, Box 19)
  - Crack Babies: Maternal and Prenatal Drug Exposure and Abuse [SJR11/HJR14] [2 of 12] (Folder 4, Box 19)
  - Crack Babies: Maternal and prenatal Drug Exposure and Abuse [SJR11/HJR14] [3 of 12] (Folder 5, Box 19)
  - Crack Babies: Maternal and prenatal Drug Exposure and Abuse [SJR11/HJR14] [4 of 12] (Folder 6, Box 19)
  - Crack Babies: Maternal and prenatal Drug Exposure and Abuse [SJR11/HJR14] [5 of 12] (Folder 7, Box 19)
  - Crack Babies: Maternal and prenatal Drug Exposure and Abuse [SJR11/HJR14] [6 of 12] (Folder 8, Box 19)
  - Crack Babies: Maternal and prenatal Drug Exposure and Abuse [SJR11/HJR14] [7 of 12] (Folder 9, Box 19)
  - Crack Babies: Maternal and prenatal Drug Exposure and Abuse [SJR11/HJR14] [8 of 12] (Folder 10, Box 19)
  - Crack Babies: Maternal and prenatal Drug Exposure and Abuse [SJR11/HJR14] [9 of 12] (Folder 11, Box 19)
  - Crack Babies: Maternal and prenatal Drug Exposure and Abuse [SJR11/HJR14] [10 of 12] (Folder 12, Box 19)
  - Crack Babies: Maternal and prenatal Drug Exposure and Abuse [SJR11/HJR14] [11 of 12] (Folder 13, Box 19)
  - Crack Babies: Maternal and prenatal Drug Exposure and Abuse [SJR11/HJR14] [12 of 12] (Folder 14, Box 19)
  - Day Care Study [1 of 4] 1989 (Folder 15, Box 19)
  - Day Care Study [2 of 4] 1989 (Folder 16, Box 19)
  - Day Care Study [3 of 4] 1989 (Folder 17, Box 19)
  - Day Care Study [4 of 4] 1989 (Folder 18, Box 19)
  - HJR 124: Early Childhood Education and Daycare Study [1 of 8] 1990 (Folder 19, Box 19)
  - HJR 124: Early Childhood Education and Daycare Study [2 of 8] 1990 (Folder 20, Box 19)
  - HJR 124: Early Childhood Education and Daycare Study [3 of 8] 1990 (Folder 21, Box 19)
  - HJR 124: Early Childhood Education and Daycare Study [4 of 8] 1990 (Folder 22, Box 19)
  - HJR 124: Early Childhood Education and Daycare Study [5 of 8] 1990 (Folder 23, Box 19)
  - HJR 124: Early Childhood Education and Daycare Study [6 of 8] 1990 (Folder 24, Box 19)
  - HJR 124: Early Childhood Education and Daycare Study [7 of 8] 1990 (Folder 25, Box 19)
  - HJR 124: Early Childhood Education and Daycare Study [8 of 8] 1990 (Folder 26, Box 19)
  - HJR 164: Early Intervention Services to Handicapped Infants and Toddlers [1 of 8] 1992 - 1993 (Folder 1, Box 20)
  - HJR 164: Early Intervention Services to Handicapped Infants and Toddlers [2 of 8] 1992 - 1993 (Folder 2, Box 20)
  - HJR 164: Early Intervention Services to Handicapped Infants and Toddlers [3 of 8] 1992 - 1993 (Folder 3, Box 20)
  - HJR 164: Early Intervention Services to Handicapped Infants and Toddlers [4 of 8] 1992 - 1993 (Folder 4, Box 20)
  - HJR 164: Early Intervention Services to Handicapped Infants and Toddlers [5 of 8] 1992 - 1993 (Folder 5, Box 20)
  - HJR 164: Early Intervention Services to Handicapped Infants and Toddlers [6 of 8] 1992 - 1993 (Folder 6, Box 20)
  - HJR 164: Early Intervention Services to Handicapped Infants and Toddlers [7 of 8] 1992 - 1993 (Folder 7, Box 20)
  - HJR 164: Early Intervention Services to Handicapped Infants and Toddlers [8 of 8] 1992 - 1993 (Folder 8, Box 20)
  - Early Intervention Study Committee [1 of 8] 1990 - 1993 (Folder 9, Box 20)
  - Early Intervention Study Committee [2 of 8] 1990 - 1993 (Folder 10, Box 20)
  - Early Intervention Study Committee [3 of 8] 1990 - 1993 (Folder 11, Box 20)
  - Early Intervention Study Committee [4 of 8] 1990 - 1993 (Folder 12, Box 20)
  - Early Intervention Study Committee [5 of 8] 1990 - 1993 (Folder 13, Box 20)
  - Early Intervention Study Committee [6 of 8] 1990 - 1993 (Folder 14, Box 20)
  - Early Intervention Study Committee [7 of 8] 1990 - 1993 (Folder 15, Box 20)
  - Early Intervention Study Committee [8 of 8] 1990 - 1993 (Folder 16, Box 20)
  - Education and Health Committee [1 of 5] 1989 (Folder 17, Box 20)
  - Education and Health Committee [2 of 5] 1989 (Folder 18, Box 20)
  - Education and Health Committee [3 of 5] 1989 (Folder 19, Box 20)
  - Education and Health Committee [4 of 5] 1989 (Folder 20, Box 20)
  - Education and Health Committee [5 of 5] 1989 (Folder 21, Box 20)
  - Education and Health,Higher Education Sub-Committee 1989 (Folder 22, Box 20)
  - Freedom of Information Act ,Joint Sub-Committee- Inactive File [1 of 4] 1988-1990 (Folder 1, Box 21)
  - Freedom of Information Act ,Joint Sub-Committee- Inactive File [2 of 4] 1988-1990 (Folder 2, Box 21)
  - Freedom of Information Act ,Joint Sub-Committee- Inactive File [3 of 4] 1988-1990 (Folder 3, Box 21)
  - Freedom of Information Act ,Joint Sub-Committee- Inactive File [4 of 4] 1988-1990 (Folder 4, Box 21)
  - Freedom of Information Act ,Joint Sub-Committee [1 of 4] 1988-1990 (Folder 5, Box 21)
  - Freedom of Information Act ,Joint Sub-Committee [2 of 4] 1988-1990 (Folder 6, Box 21)
  - Freedom of Information Act ,Joint Sub-Committee [3 of 4] 1988-1990 (Folder 7, Box 21)
  - Freedom of Information Act ,Joint Sub-Committee [4 of 4] 1988-1990 (Folder 8, Box 21)
  - General Laws Committee [1 of 2] 1989 (Folder 9, Box 21)
  - General Laws Committee [2 of 2] 1989 (Folder 10, Box 21)
  - Guardianship ,Joint Sub-Committee Study (Folder 11, Box 21)
  - Local Government Committee [1 of 4] 1989 (Folder 12, Box 21)
  - Local Government Committee [2 of 4] 1989 (Folder 13, Box 21)
  - Local Government Committee [3 of 4] 1989 (Folder 14, Box 21)
  - Local Government Committee [4 of 4] 1989 (Folder 15, Box 21)
  - Local Government Committee Transfer Development Rights Study [1 of 10] 1989 (Folder 16, Box 21)
  - Local Government Committee Transfer Development Rights Study [2 of 10] 1989 (Folder 17, Box 21)
  - Local Government Committee Transfer Development Rights Study [3 of 10] 1989 (Folder 18, Box 21)
  - Local Government Committee Transfer Development Rights Study [4 of 10] 1989 (Folder 19, Box 21)
  - Local Government Committee Transfer Development Rights Study [5 of 10] 1989 (Folder 20, Box 21)
  - Local Government Committee Transfer Development Rights Study [6 of 10] 1989 (Folder 21, Box 21)
  - Local Government Committee Transfer Development Rights Study [7 of 10] 1989 (Folder 22, Box 21)
  - Local Government Committee Transfer Development Rights Study [8 of 10] 1989 (Folder 23, Box 21)
  - Local Government Committee Transfer Development Rights Study [9 of 10] 1989 (Folder 24, Box 21)
  - Local Government Committee Transfer Development Rights Study [10 of 10] 1989 (Folder 25, Box 21)
  - NCSL Task Force on Developmental Disabilities [1 of 15] 1989 - 1992 (Folder 1, Box 22)
  - NCSL Task Force on Developmental Disabilities [2 of 15] 1989 - 1992 (Folder 2, Box 22)
  - NCSL Task Force on Developmental Disabilities [3 of 15] 1989 - 1992 (Folder 3, Box 22)
  - NCSL Task Force on Developmental Disabilities [4 of 15] 1989 - 1992 (Folder 4, Box 22)
  - NCSL Task Force on Developmental Disabilities [5 of 15] 1989 - 1992 (Folder 5, Box 22)
  - NCSL Task Force on Developmental Disabilities [6 of 15] 1989 - 1992 (Folder 6, Box 22)
  - NCSL Task Force on Developmental Disabilities [7 of 15] 1989 - 1992 (Folder 7, Box 22)
  - NCSL Task Force on Developmental Disabilities [8 of 15] 1989 - 1992 (Folder 8, Box 22)
  - NCSL Task Force on Developmental Disabilities [9 of 15] 1989 - 1992 (Folder 9, Box 22)
  - NCSL Task Force on Developmental Disabilities [10 of 15] 1989 - 1992 (Folder 10, Box 22)
  - NCSL Task Force on Developmental Disabilities [11 of 15] 1989 - 1992 (Folder 11, Box 22)
  - NCSL Task Force on Developmental Disabilities [12 of 15] 1989 - 1992 (Folder 12, Box 22)
  - NCSL Task Force on Developmental Disabilities [13 of 15] 1989 - 1992 (Folder 13, Box 22)
  - NCSL Task Force on Developmental Disabilities [14 of 15] 1989 - 1992 (Folder 14, Box 22)
  - NCSL Task Force on Developmental Disabilities [15 of 15] 1989 - 1992 (Folder 15, Box 22)
  - NCSL Task Force Developmental Disabilities: 1990 Report to Congress 1990 (Folder 16, Box 22)
  - Senate Finance Committee [1 of 4] 1988 (Folder 17, Box 22)
  - Senate Finance Committee [2 of 4] 1988 (Folder 18, Box 22)
  - Senate Finance Committee [3 of 4] 1988 (Folder 19, Box 22)
  - Senate Finance Committee [4 of 4] 1988 (Folder 20, Box 22)
  - Special Education [1 of 7] 1988 (Folder 21, Box 22)
  - Special Education [2 of 7] 1988 (Folder 22, Box 22)
  - Special Education [3 of 7] 1988 (Folder 23, Box 22)
  - Special Education [4 of 7] 1988 (Folder 24, Box 22)
  - Northern Virginia Delegation Presentation October 17,1991 (Folder 25, Box 22)
  - Special Education [5 of 7] 1988 (Folder 1, Box 23)
  - Special Education [6 of 7] 1988 (Folder 2, Box 23)
  - Special Education [7 of 7] 1988 (Folder 3, Box 23)
  - Surrogate Motherhood Study [1 of 6] 1989 (Folder 4, Box 23)
  - Surrogate Motherhood Study [2 of 6] 1989 (Folder 5, Box 23)
  - Surrogate Motherhood Study [3 of 6] 1989 (Folder 6, Box 23)
  - Surrogate Motherhood Study [4 of 6] 1989 (Folder 7, Box 23)
  - Surrogate Motherhood Study [5 of 6] 1989 (Folder 8, Box 23)
  - Surrogate Motherhood Study [6 of 6] 1989 (Folder 9, Box 23)
  - Transfer Development Rights and Land Use Study [1 of 7] 1988 - 1992 (Folder 10, Box 23)
  - Transfer Development Rights and Land Use Study [2 of 7] 1988 - 1992 (Folder 11, Box 23)
  - Transfer Development Rights and Land Use Study [3 of 7] 1988 - 1992 (Folder 12, Box 23)